<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<knowl mode="exercise" xmlns="https://spatext.clontz.org" version="0.2">
    <!-- {{#cards}} -->
        <content>
            <p>
                Rowan and Collen each put $<m>{{pool}}</m> into the pot.  Then 4 Jacks, 4 Queens and 4 Kings are shuffled, and then one card each is dealt to Rowan and Colleen.  They may each see their own card but not their opponents.
                Rowan may either fold, in which case Colleen takes the entire pot, or they may raise by $<m>{{bet}}</m>, putting this value into the pot.  If Rowan raises, then either Colleen folds, in which case Rowan takes the pot, or calls, also placing
                $<m>{{bet}}</m> into the pot.  If Colleen calls, both player reveals their cards, and the player with the higher card (with Jack &lt; Queen &lt; King) takes the pot. In the case of a tie they split the pot.

            </p>
            <p>
                Write out the payoff matrix for this game.
            </p>
        </content>
        <outtro>
            <p>
                <me>
                    \begin{array}{ r| {{#C}} {{c}} {{/C}} | }
                    {{#col}} &amp; {{col}} {{/col}} \\
                    \hline
                    {{#data}}
                        {{row}}
                        {{#data2}}
                          &amp;  {{entry}} 
                        {{/data2}}
                        \\
                    {{/data}}
                    \hline
                    \end{array}
                </me>
            </p>
        </outtro>  
    <!-- {{/cards}} -->
    <!-- {{#difference}} -->
        <content>
            <p>
                Each player Rowan and Colleen selects  a number from <m>1</m> through <m>{{n}}</m> and reveals them at the same time.
                If the difference between selections is less than <m>{{m}}</m>, the player with the larger number wins points
                equal to the sum of the selections.
                Otherwise the player with the smaller number wins points
                equal to the sum of the selections.
                If the selections are equal, neither player wins any points.
            </p>
            <p>
                Write out the payoff matrix for this game.
            </p>
        </content>
        <outtro>
            <p>
                <me>
                    \begin{array}{ r| {{#C}} {{c}} {{/C}} | }
                    {{#col}} &amp; {{col}} {{/col}} \\
                    \hline
                    {{#data}}
                        {{row}}
                        {{#data2}}
                          &amp;  {{entry}} 
                        {{/data2}}
                        \\
                    {{/data}}
                    \hline
                    \end{array}
                </me>
            </p>
        </outtro>  
    <!-- {{/difference}} -->
    <!-- {{#blotto}} -->
        <content>
            <p>
                Colonel Rowan is attacking a town defended by Colonel Colleen. 
                Rowan has <m>{{Rtroop}}</m> regiments and Colleen has <m>{{Ctroop}}</m>. 
                There are two routes to the town. 
                Rowan and select any number of regiments to attack along each route, up to a total of <m>{{Rtroop}}</m>
                 and Colleen can likewise assign her <m>{{Ctroop}}</m> regiments along either route, neither knowing beforehand the other's strategy.
            </p>
            <p>
                Along each route, whatever side has a greater number of regiments wins points equal to the 
                number of regiments sent by the opposing side (as they capture those units). 
                Furthermore, if Rowan wins along either route, he captures the town also worth one point.
            </p>
            <p>
                Write out the payoff matrix for this game.
            </p>
        </content>
        <outtro>
            <p>
                <me>
                    \begin{array}{ r| {{#C}} {{c}} {{/C}} | }
                    {{#col}} &amp; {{col}} {{/col}} \\
                    \hline
                    {{#data}}
                        {{row}}
                        {{#data2}}
                          &amp;  {{entry}} 
                        {{/data2}}
                        \\
                    {{/data}}
                    \hline
                    \end{array}
                </me>
            </p>
        </outtro>  
    <!-- {{/blotto}} -->

    <!-- {{#evenodd}} -->
        <content>
            <p>
                Each player Rowan and Colleen selects  a number from <m>1</m> through <m>{{n}}</m> and reveals them at the same time.
                If they are the same, Rowan pays Colleen a number of dollars equal to the sum of the selections.
                If they are different but the sum is even, Rowan pays Collen dollars equal to the difference between selections.
                Otherwise the Colleen pays Rowan $<m>{{n}}</m>.
            </p>
            <p>
                Write out the payoff matrix for this game.
            </p>
        </content>
        <outtro>
            <p>
                <me>
                    \begin{array}{ r| {{#C}} {{c}} {{/C}} | }
                    {{#col}} &amp; {{col}} {{/col}} \\
                    \hline
                    {{#data}}
                        {{row}}
                        {{#data2}}
                          &amp;  {{entry}} 
                        {{/data2}}
                        \\
                    {{/data}}
                    \hline
                    \end{array}
                </me>
            </p>
        </outtro>  
    <!-- {{/evenodd}} -->
</knowl>



    